Luciano Nicolás Díaz

Buenos Aires, Buenos Aires Province, Argentina



luchodiaz1995@gmail.com



01159102957



linkedin.com/in/lucianonicolasdiaz

Summary

I am a Full Stack developer with industry experience building websites and web applications. I specialize in .NET and have professional experience working with C#, REST APIs and JavaScript. I also have experience working with jQuery, CSS, HTML5, MS SQL Server and using Angular as framework. I aim to specialize on Angular + .NET stack.

Experience



🧃 Full Stack Developer

IUDÚ

Mar 2022 - Present (3 months +)

- Following the Scrum methodology, using Jira.
- Maintenance and Development of the On Boarding section from the app hosted on the Play/App Store (IUDÚ).
- Maintenance and Development of an internal system from the company to allow the users to check the status of the new on boardings from the clients.
- Work in Squads.
- Use especially MS Sql Server, .Net Core 3.1, Angular, and Git (with respositories alocated on Azure Dev Ops).

Full Stack Developer

Globant

May 2021 - Mar 2022 (11 months)

- Following the Scrum methodology, using Jira (Talking on English).
- Maintenance and Development of a platform for the sale of advertising space.
- Unit Testing (Karma, Jasmine, NUnit).
- Work in PODs.
- Use .Net Framework, JavaScript, jQuery and Git (with respositories alocated on Azure Dev Ops).

Full Stack Developer

Time Solution Software

Feb 2020 - Apr 2021 (1 year 3 months)

- Development and maintenance of an E-Commerce.
- Development and maintenance of Web Desktops. (Windows Forms).
- Managment and development of Data Bases.
- Communication team through Discord and Trello.
- Work using Git for our code and push to a GitHub respository.
- Use .Net Framework 4.5, Web Forms, Web Api, Windows Forms, C#, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, jQuery, Ms Sql Server, T-SQL.

Education

∗∪TN Universidad Tecnológica Nacional

University Technician in Computer Systems, Systems Engineering Mar 2020 - Mar 2021

*UTN Universidad Tecnológica Nacional

University Technician in Programming, Computer Software Engineering Mar 2018 - Mar 2020